# JUSTIN GRISWOLD

3708 Round Hill Road Apt 11 Swansea, IL 62226 · 314-471-7133

JaGriswold0@gmail.com

github.com/JGrisw

An avid learner, quick to apply new skills in a team atmosphere to design efficient projects. Use of experience as a production manager delegating and managing multiple projects with consistently meeting deadlines. Swift understanding of new technologies and planning multi-stage company wide launch. Proven troubleshooter on tight deadlines utilizing multiple software platforms to ensure success

#### **EXPERIENCE**

JULY 2018 - AUGUST 20TH 2021

#### FACILITY PRODUCTION MANAGER, UNITED FULFILLMENT SOLUTIONS

#### ST. LOUIS, MO

- Oversee all aspects of production throughout facilities across the US
- Directly supervise employees, delegating tasks to maximize productivity and minimize production overhead
- Maintain Service Level Agreements with multiple clients, including but not limited to 99% accuracy and on time shipping
- Coordinate structure and set up of new facilities in multiple states
- Assist in interviewing and onboarding of new employees
- Assist in implementing a new warehouse distribution system, trained employees on the updated process
- Maintain relationships with carrier services such as UPS, DHL, FedEx, and USPS
- ISO, USDA, GMP certified

**FEBRUARY 2018 – JULY 2018** 

#### **OPERATIONS SUPERVISOR, COLDCO LOGISTICS**

#### FAIRMONT CITY, IL

- Directed main operations team
- Oversee inventory management
- Restructured operations floor to accommodate increase in production

**MARCH 2013 - FEBRUARY 2018** 

#### **INTEGRATION COORDINATION SPECIALIST, UNITED FULFILLMENT SOLUTIONS**

#### ST. LOUIS, MO

- Onboard new clientele into distribution and fulfillment chains
- Assist in restructuring warehouse layout to streamline operations productivity
- Maintain functionality of equipment
- Supervise production of satellite facilities during transitionary periods

### **EDUCATION**

2007 HARRINGTON INSTITUTION OF DESIGN CHICAGO, IL

AUGUST 2021 – MARCH 2022
LAUNCHCODE
CERTIFICATION IN JAVA/JAVASCRIPT
ST. LOUIS, MO

# **SKILLS**

- Process oriented
- Management and delegation
- Record keeping
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- Angular
- HTML
- CSS

- Organization
- Time management
- Project administration
- Java
- Thymeleaf
- Spring Boot
- SQL

# **ACTIVITIES**

Studying, Exercising, Photography, Baking, multiple years volunteering for the Salvation Army including Kettle bell donations seasons coordinating employee schedules, youth programs and Harbor light homeless programs.

# **REFERENCES**

Brittany Babb Recruiter at Meta 618-791-0702 Brittanybabb24@gmail.com

Chris Miller
Operations Manager at Coldco Logistics
618-719-6348
Cmiller0810@Gmail.com

Kelli Stricklin Customer Service Representative at Concordia Plan Services 314-775-3090 Kelli.Stricklin25@gmail.com

Victoria Rodriguez Senior Talent Acquisition Support Specialist at Edward Jones 618-402-2431 VeeRod0804@yahoo.com

Sean Cantor
Account Coordinator and EDI Specialist at United Fulfilment Solutions 314-607-9636
Anubisaxe@yahoo.com